Herold J. Wiens Collection
Geography & Map Division Library of Congress
Herold J. Wiens Collection1941-ca. 1979
G7821.S7 coll.W5 Wiens
Wiens, Herold J., 1912-1971.
264 pieces chiefly maps charts, and views
Scales differ.
Geography & Map Division Library of Congress Washington, DC
Consists of pen and ink drawings, pencil sketches, facsimiles, and photographs of aerial views showing all or part of China during the period of World War II. The collection also consists of technical drawing equipment, notes, charts, atlases, some books, personal folders, letters, correspondence, and other miscellaneous items.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically therein.
People
Wiens, Herold J. (Herold Jacob), 1912-1971.
Subjects
World War, 1939-1945--Asia--Maps.; World War, 1939-1945--China--Charts, diagrams, etc.; World War, 1939-1945--China--Maps.
Places
Marshall Islands--Remote-sensing images.
Administrative Information
Provenance
Gift; Mi Chu.
Accruals
No further accruals are expected.
Scope and Content Note
The Herold J. Wiens Collection consists of pen and ink drawings, pencil sketches, facsimiles, and photographs of aerial views showing all or part of China during the period of World War II. The collection also consists of technical drawing equipment, notes, charts, atlases, some books, personal folders, letters, correspondence, and other miscellaneous items. Covers China, Marshall Islands (1951-1952), and parts of Asia. On pilot maps shows graphic flight line index.
Biographical Note
Herold J. Wiens was born in Shanghang, Fukien Province (China) on Dec. 26, 1912. His ancestors were Mennonites from the Netherlands. Mennonite migration brought the Wiens family to Russia, to the United States and then to China in 1910.
Herold Wiens was educated and lived in China until he was fourteen years old at which time his family moved to Reedley, California. During his formative years in China, Wiens developed a knowledge of Chinese culture, and became fluent in Mandarin Chinese and the Hakka dialect. He attended Reedley High School where he graduated in 1931. He received his undergraduate college education at the University of California (Berkeley).
In 1936, Wiens returned to China for advanced study and research at Yenching University in Beijing. There he studied with several of most noted China specialists from the United States. Before returning to the United States in 1940, Wiens worked at the U.S. Embassy in Hankou and Chungking for two years. During World War II he worked in the American Embassy in Chongqing, returning to the United States in 1946. His war-time correspondence and reports gave vivid accounts of the bombing and devastation in war-time China.
Wiens began graduate school in 1946 at the University of Michigan and completed M.A. and Ph.D. programs, graduating in 1949. His celebrated academic career included a nineteen year tenure at Yale University, three years at the University of Hawaii, and one year at Northern Illinois University in DeKalb. He was awarded Fulbright Fellowships twice, once in 1961 and again in 1964, and he was a recipient of a Guggenheim Fellowship. He was one of the most accomplished China geographers of his generation and he educated many young scholars at the three universities where he taught. Professor Wiens died on September 15, 1971.
Herold Wiens’ biography can be found in Adina Wiens Robinson, China Beckoning (Oakland, Calif.: Positive Press, 1991); and Hao-jan Chu, “Biography of Herold J. Wiens,” in Biographical Literature, 19:6 (December, 1971), Taipei, Taiwan.
Publications
Asia with focus on China / by Herold J. Wiens and Margaret Fisher Hertel. -- Grand Rapids: Fideler Co., [1964] 260 p.: ill., maps (part col.), ports,; 25 cm. -- (Depth-study textbooks) Bibliography: p. 248.
Atoll environment and ecology. New Haven, Yale University Press: 1962. xxii, 532 p. illus., maps, charts. 24 cm. (SIM report; no. 27) Bibliography: p. 485-504.
China.-- Grand Rapids, Fideler: [1962] 192 p. illus., maps. 28 cm. (Life in other lands)
China [by] Herold J. Wiens. -- Grand Rapids: Fideler Co., 1965. 192 p. illus., maps. 28 cm. Summary: A textbook for the upper elementary grades. Describes the land, people, and life of Communist China, a country of nearly eight hundred million inhabitants.
China.--Grand Rapids, Fideler Co.: 1966. 160 p. ill., maps. –(Life in other lands)
China [by] Herold J. Wiens. Grand Rapids, Fideler Co.: [1967] 192 p. illus., maps. 28 cm.
China. Kit.-- Grand Rapids, Mich.: Fideler Visual Teaching, c1970. 45 social studies pictures and visual teaching text. (A social studies picture program)
[China's march into the tropics] China's march toward the tropics; a discussion of the southward penetration of China's culture, peoples, and political control in relation to the non-Han-Chinese peoples of south China and in the perspective of historical and cultural geography, by Herold J. Wiens. Hamden, Conn., Shoe String Press: [1954]. xv, 441 p.: illus., maps. 23 cm. First published in 1952 under title: China's march into the tropics. "Bibliographical references": p. [373]-389. "Bibliographical references in Chinese language": p. [391]-393.
China's march into the tropics; a discussion of the southward penetration of China's culture, peoples, and political control in relation to the non-Han-Chinese peoples of South China and in the perspective of historical and cultural geography. Prepared under the auspices of the Office of Naval Research, United States Navy, Washington, 1952. iii, 221 p. ill., maps. 28 cm. Includes bibliographies.
[China's march into the tropics] Han Chinese expansion in South China, by Herold J. Wiens. [Hamden, Conn.]: Shoe String Press, 1967 [c1954] xv, 441 p. illus., maps. 22 cm. "Originally published under the title: China's march toward the tropics"--T.p. verso.
China's march into the tropics [microform]: a discussion of the southward penetration of China's culture, peoples, and political control in relation to the non-Han-Chinese peoples of South China and in the perspective of historical and cultural geography / Prepared under the auspices of the Office of Naval Research, United States Navy, by Herold J. Wiens. Washington, D.C.: U.S. Dept. of Commerce, Office of Technical Services, 1952. iii, 221 p., 34 leaves of plates: maps. Bibliography: p. 217-219. Microfilm. Washington, D.C.: Library of Congress, Photoduplication Service, 1954. 1 microfilm reel; 35 mm. Low reduction.
China's march toward the tropics; a discussion of the southward penetration of China's culture, peoples, and political control in relation to the non-Han- Chinese peoples of south China and in the perspective of historical and cultural geography. Hamden, Conn.: Shoe String Press [1954]. xv, 441 p.: illus., maps. 23 cm. First published in 1952 under title: China's march into the tropics. "Bibliographical references": p. [373]-389. "Bibliographical references in Chinese language": p. [391]-393.
China's march toward the tropics: a discussion of the southward penetration of China's culture, peoples, and political control in relation to the non-Han- Chinese peoples of south China and in the perspective of historical and cultural geography / by Herold J. Wiens. Hamden, Conn.: Shoe String Press, c1954. xv, 441 p.: ill., maps.; 23 cm. First published in 1952 under title: China's march into the tropics. Includes bibliographical references and index.
Field notes on atolls visited in the Marshalls, 1956 / by Herold J. Wiens. Washington, D.C.: Pacific Science Board, National Academy of Sciences-- National Research Council, 1957. 23 p.; 28 cm. (Atoll research bulletin; no. 54)
The geography of Kapingamarangi atoll in the eastern Carolines. New Haven, Conn.: Yale University, 1955. ii, 86 [8] p. illus., maps (part fold.) (Scientific Investigations in Micronesia. Report, no. 21) Bibliography: p.[94]
The geographical environment of the Narragansett Bay Region / Herold J. Wiens. 1953. 25 leaves: ill.; 28 cm.–(Technical memorandum no. 16; (ESL:421:Serial 2)), 27 April 1953. Edwards Street Laboratory, Yale University, New Haven, Connecticut." TM 16, NR-238-001. Contract Nonr-609(02)" Includes bibliographical references.
The geography of Kapingamarangi Atoll in the Eastern Carolines. Washington, D.C.: National Academy of Sciences, National Research Council, Pacific science board, June 30, 1956. ii, [92] p. tables. 27 cm.–(Atoll research bulletin, no. 48)
The geography of Kapingamarangi atoll in the eastern Carolines. New Haven, Conn.: Yale University, 1955. ii, 86 [8] p. ill., maps (part fold.)–(Scientific Investigations in Micronesia. Report, no. 21) Bibliography: p.[94]
Han Chinese expansion in South China, by Herold J. Wiens.--[Hamden, Conn.]: Shoe String Press, 1967 [c1954] xv, 441 p. ill., maps. 22 cm. Reprint of the 1954 ed. which was a revision of a work first published in 1952 under title: China's march into the tropics. Includes bibliographies.
Mongolia, by Herold J. Wiens. [Prepared with the co-operation of the American Geographical Society. Garden City, N.Y.: Doubleday, 1967] 63 p. ill. (part col.), col. maps, col. plates. 21 cm. (Around the world program)
Pacific island bastions of the United States. Princeton, N.J.: Van Nostrand, [1962] iv, 127 p. ill. 20 cm. (Van Nostrand searchlight books, #4)
Pacific island bastions of the United States / by Herold J. Wiens. Westport, Conn.: Greenwood Press, 1984, c1962. iv, 127 p.: maps; 23 cm. Reprint. Originally published: Princeton, N.J.: Van Nostrand, c1962. Bibliography: p. 123-124. Includes index. ISBN 0313243883 (lib. bdg.)
Pacific island bastions of the United States. Princeton, N.J.: Van Nostrand [1962] 127 p. illus. (Van Nostrand searchlight books, #4)
The Shu Tao, or the road to Szechuan; a study of the development and significance of Shensi-Szechuan road communication in West China. 1948. 200 leaves, fold. map in pocket at back.-- Reproduced from typewritten copy. Thesis, University of Michigan. Bibliography: leaves 194-200.
The Shu Tao, or, The road to Szechuan [microform]: a study of the development of Sheni-Szechuan road communication in west China. -- Ann Arbor, MI: University Microfilms, 1948. Microfilm copy of typewritten ms. Made in 1948 by University Microflims (Publication no. 1122) Positive. Collation of the original: 200 leaves, ill., maps (part folded) 30 cm. Thesis--University of Michigan. Abstracted in Dissertation abstracts, v. 9 (1949) no. 1, p. 116-117. Bibliography: leaves 194-200.
Some effects of geographic location upon land utilization in the coral atolls of Micronesia / Herold J. Wiens.--[s.l.: s.n.], 1963. p. 157-162. 26 cm. Bibliography: p. 162.
Organization of the Herold J. Wiens Collection
The Herold J. Wiens Collection is organized in 1 series:
Maps from Herold J. Wiens
http://lccn.loc.gov/2004627525
Container List
- [Siagwan, Fujian, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 20, 1944., 1; 95 Aerial Photographs and 1 index. 26 x 26 cm.; 1:15,000; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by graphic flight line index [incomplete].; "Sortie 35PR 4MH 29. Height 30,000 ft."; Southwest corner coordinate: "North 26o East 119o "; Access Points: China Fujian
- [Guangdong, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, April 17, 1945., 2; 8 Aerial Aerial Photographs and 1 index. 26 x 26 cm.; 1:60,000; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by graphic flight line index.; "Sortie 35PR 5 ME 64. Height 30,000 ft."; "North 23o East 113o "; Access Points: China. Guangdong
- [Zhejiang, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 15, 1944., 3; 20 Aerial Aerial Photographs and 2 indexes. 26 x 26 cm.; 1:14,500 and 1:29,000; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by graphic flight line index.; "Sortie 35PR 4MH 28. Height 29,000 ft."; "North 29o East 121o "; Access Points: China. Zhejiang
- [Zhejiang, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 19, 1944., 4; 42 Aerial Aerial Photographs and 1 index. 26 x 26 cm.; 1:15,000; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by graphic flight line index.; "Sortie 35PR 4MH 27. Height 30,000 ft.; "North 29o East 121o "; Access Points: China. Zhejiang
- [Fujian, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, May 10, 1945., 5; 12 Aerial Aerial Photographs and 1 index. 26 x 26 cm.; 1:15,000; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by graphic flight line index [incomplete] and area descriptions on back of photographs; "Sortie 25PR 5M 130. Height 30,000 ft."; "North 26o East 119o "; Access Points: China. Fujian
- [Guangdong, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, July 25, 1945., 6; 34 Aerial Photographs and 1 index. 26 x 26 cm.; 1:9,750; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by graphic flight line index [incomplete].; "Sortie 35PR 5MF 40. Height 19,500 ft."; "North 23o East 113o "; Access Points: China. Guangdong
- [Zhejiang, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, June 15, 1945., 7; 15 Aerial Photographs and 4 indexes. 51 x 26 cm.; 1:13,000; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by graphic flight line index [incomplete].; "Sortie 21PR 5MD 138. Height 26,000 ft."; "North 28o East 120o "; Access Points: China. Zhejiang
- [Guangdong, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, October 16, 1944., 8; 53 Aerial Photographs and 2 indexes. 26 x 26 cm.; 1:10,500; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by graphic flight line index [incomplete].; "Sortie 21PR 4MB 243. Height 21,000 ft."; "North 23o East 116o "; Access Points: China. Guangdong
- [Tienho, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, March 10, 1944., 9; 3 Aerial Photographs and 1 index. 26 x 26 cm.; 1:56,000; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by graphic flight line index [incomplete].; "Sortie 21PR 4MB 19. Height 28,000 ft."; "North 23o East 113o "; Access Points: China. Tienho
- [Tienho, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, March 10, 1944., 10; 15 Aerial Photographs and 1 index. 51 x 26 cm.; 1:14,000; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by graphic flight line index.; "Sortie 21PR 4MB 19. Height 28,000 ft."; "North 23o East 113o "; Access Points: China. Tienho
- [Zhejiang, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, September 18, 1944., 11; 8 Aerial Photographs and 1 index. 51 x 26 cm.; 1:15,000; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by graphic flight line index.; "Sortie 21PR 4MB 19. Height 28,000 ft."; "North 29o East 121o "; Access Points: China. Zhejiang
- [White Cloud, Guangdong, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, April 12, 1945., 12; 7 Aerial Photographs and 1 index. 51 x 26 cm.; 1:60,000; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by graphic flight line index.; "Sortie 21PR 4MD 192. Height 30,000 ft."; "North 23o East 113o "; Access Points: China. White Cloud, Guangdong
- [Zhejiang, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, June 15, 1945., 13; 21 Aerial Photographs and 1 index. 26 x 26 cm.; 1:7,879; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by graphic flight line index; "Sortie 21PR 5MD 138. Height 26,000 ft."; "North 28o East 120o "; Access Points: China Zhejiang
- [China-Vietnam Border] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 14; 2 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by written description of area.; "Sortie 35PR 4MF 5,17", Height Unknown.; "North 22o 20' East 106o 5' "; Access Points: China. Vietnam
- [China-Vietnam Border] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 15; 1 Aerial Photograph 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by written description of area.; "Sortie 35PR 5MH 84". Height Unknown.; "North 22o 40' East 106o 13' "; Access Points: Vietnam Caobang
- [Hanoi, Vietnam] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 16; 1 Aerial Photograph 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by written description of area.; "Sortie 35PR 5MG 46." Height Unknown.; "North 21o East 106o "; Access Points: Viet Nam. Hanoi
- [Vietnam-China Border] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 17; 1 Aerial Photograph 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by written description of area.; "Sortie 35 PR 5M? 45." Height Unknown.; "North 22o 35' East 103o 50' "; Access Points: China Kwanghsi Province
- [Fujian, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 18; 112 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie 35PR 4MH 30." Height 30,000 ft.; "North 26o 53' East 119o 20' "; Access Points: China. Fujian
- [Fujian, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 19; 21 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie 35PR 4MH 30." Height 30,000 ft.; "North 26o 25' East 119o 40' "; Access Points: China. Fujian
- [Hunan, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 20; 1 Aerial Photograph 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; "Sortie 35 PR 5ME 138." Height 17,500 ft.; "North 26o 10' East 113o 34' "; Access Points: China. Hunan
- [China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 21; 1 Aerial Photograph 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; "Sortie 35PR 5MH 37." Height Unknown.; Access Points: China.
- [China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 22; 1 Aerial Photograph 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; "Sortie 35PR 5MH 25." Height Unknown.; Access Points: China.
- [Yon Hsien, Hunan, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 23; 3 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie 35PR 5MH 27." Height Unknown.; Access Points: China. Yon Hsien
- [Salween River, Chihtaoho, Burma] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 24; 3 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie 9PRS 4MA 33." Height 20,000 ft.; "North 25o East 99o "; Access Points: Burma.
- [Tengshung Road to Sadow, Yunnan, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 25; 1 Aerial Photograph 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; "Sortie 9PRS 4MA 11." Height 21,300 ft.; "North 25o 00' East 98o 30' "; Access Points: China Teng-chung, Yunnan
- [Sumprabum, Burma] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 26; 1 Aerial Photograph 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by a written description of area.; "Sortie 19PRS 5MA 40." Height Unknown.; "North 26o 33' East 97o 34' "; Access Points: Burma. Sumprabum
- [Teng-chang, Yunnan, China and Kunlong, Burma] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 27; 9 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by some written descriptions of the area.; "Sortie 21PS M12/2A." Height Unknown.; "North 23o 25' East 98o 39' "; Access Points: China Burma
- [Fort Harrison (Sadon), Burma] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 24, 1943., 28; 2 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Accompanied by a written descriptions of area.; "Sortie 21PRS M12/22A". Height Unknown.; "North 25o 13' East 97o 54' "; Access Points: Burma. Fort Harrison
- [Tianhe, Guangdong, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, September 2, 1943., 29; 17 Aerial Photographs 51 x 26 cm.; 1:15,450; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie 21PS M9/3." Height 30,900 ft.; "North 23o 8' East 113o 20' "; Access Points: China. Guangdong
- [Pao-shan and Kao-li-tungshan,Yunnan, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force,.., 30; 3 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie 21PR 4MA 39." Height Unknown.; "North 25o 7' East 99o 10' "; Access Points: China. Yunnan
- [Fort Hertz (Putao), Burma] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, October 5,1943., 31; 4 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs, some descriptions. Mentions Khamti Shan settlement.; Sortie identification number not given.; "North 27o 26' East 97o 24' "; Access Points: Burma Fort Hertz
- [Yunnan, China and Namhka, Burma] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 32; 8 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs, some descriptions. Mentions 1941.; Sortie Unknown "Height 22,000 ft".; "North 22o 25' East 99o 20' "; Access Points: China. Burma
- [Canton (Guangzhou), China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 5, 1942., 33; 6 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie Unknown "Height 25,000 ft."; "North 23o East 113o "; Access Points: China. Guangzhou
- [Canton (Guangzhou), (Guangdong), China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, August 5, 1943., 34; 5 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given.; Access Points: China. Guangzhou,Yunnan
- [Lu- shui, Yunnan, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 35; 2 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with descriptions.; "Sortie 4MA 66 LO81. Height 26,000 ft."; "North 25o 50' East 98o 52' "; Access Points: China. Burma
- [Hunan, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 36; 1 Aerial Photograph 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; "Sortie 21PR 4MB109. Height 15,000 ft."; "North 27o 48' East 113o 0' "; Access Points: China. Hunnan
- [Maingkwan, Burma] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 37; 2 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; Sortie identification number not given.; "North 26o 18' East 96o 36' "; Access Points: Burma. Maingkwan
- [Htawgaw and Hpimaw, Burma and Yunan, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, October 26, 1943., 38; 4 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with detailed descriptions.; "Sortie 21PRS M10/31A." Height Unknown.; "North 25o 57' East 98o 22' "; Access Points: Burma. Htawgaw and Hpimaw
- [Hkamti Long (Hkamtu Patau), Burma] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, March 10, 1943., 39; 4 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with one description.; "Sortie 69-153-9PS. Height 20,000 ft."; "North 27o 26' East 97o 24' "; Access Points: Burma. Hkamti Long (Hkamtu Patau)
- [Pang Long, Burma] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 40; 2 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph with a description.; "Sortie 24CMS-5M." Height Unknown.; "North 23o 15' East 98o 47' "; Access Points: Burma. Pang Long
- [Than Thuy, Vietnam] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 41; 3 Aerial Photographs 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with two descriptions.; "Sortie 24CMS:5M9." Height Unknown.; "North 22o 55' East 104o 51' "; Access Points: Vietnam. Than Thuy
- [Fu-hai, Yunnan, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 42; 1 Aerial Photograph 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; "Sortie 21PR 4MA30." Height Unknown.; Access Points: China. Fu-hai, Yunnan
- [Teng-yueh City, Yunnan, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, 1944., 43; 1 Aerial Photograph 35 x 28 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; Sortie identification number not given.; Access Points: China. Teng-yueh City, Yunnan